{
  "test": [
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1812 года?",
      "response": "1812"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1813 года?",
      "response": "1813"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1814 года?",
      "response": "1814"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1815 года?",
      "response": "1815"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1816 года?",
      "response": "1816"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1817 года?",
      "response": "1817"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1814 года?",
      "response": "1814"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1815 года?",
      "response": "1815"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1816 года?",
      "response": "1816"
    },
    {
      "question": "В каком году была война 1817 года?",
      "response": "1817"
    }
  ]
}